Week 14. Day 1. Formerly taboo entertainment. Formerly.
Pastime. Be thought of as. Be seen as. Wicked. Medieval. Dice.
In secret. Immoral. Get somebody in trouble. Day 2.
How were dogs domesticated? Domesticate. Wolf. Berry. Orphan. Cub. Offspring.
Evolve into. Eventually. Day 3. Wind power. Long-lasting. Source. Potential.
Electricity. Turbine. Fuel. Self-reliant. Power grid. Drawback. Landscape. Disrupt.
Pattern. Day 4. Johann Sebastian Bach. Composer. Innovator. Mature. Instrument. Composition.
Employ. Broaden. Influence. Explore. Melody. Master. Counterpoint. Harmony. Height.
Dedication. Day 5. The plane of jars. Oasis. Unexplainable. Rolling. In the distance. Sink. Tip. Lid. Disappear. Plate.
Scatter. Legend. Clay. Ash. Indication. Rough. Charming. Day 6. Pros and cons of coffee. Pros and cons. Practically.
When it comes to. Caffeine. Wake. In the long term. Kidney. Liver. On the flip side. Contribute to. Cholesterol. Circumstance. Day 7.
Saving animals. One species at a time. Cross one's fingers. Swamp. Alligator. Endangered.
Symbol. Dwindle. Nest. Takeover. Pesticide. Steadily. Stewardship. Slither. Treaty. Convention.
Enforcement. Pangolin.